{
    "1": {"question": "What are the 2 layers of the skin called?", "answer": "Epidermis = outer layer, dermis = inner layer"},
    "2": {"question": "What is the term for classic dandruff?", "answer": "Pityriasis Capitis Simplex"},
    "3": {"question": "What is the technical term for ringworm?", "answer": "Tinea"},
    "4": {"question": "What is the technical term for an inflammatory skin condition?", "answer": "Dermatitis"},
    "5": {"question": "What is another name for a blackhead?", "answer": "Acne, open comedones"},
    "6": {"question": "Which direction are your manipulations for facials?", "answer": "Effleurage - light upward motion, toward the origin of the muscle."},
    "7": {"question": "What are the 4 types of skin?", "answer": "Normal, oily, dry, or combination"},
    "8": {"question": "What is the protein that makes up nails?", "answer": "Keratin"},
    "9": {"question": "What are the 4 different facial manipulations?", "answer": "Effleurage, petrissage, tapotement, massager/vibrator"},
    "10": {"question": "What does your fingernail rest on?", "answer": "Nail bed"},
    "11": {"question": "Where is your hyponychium and eponychium?", "answer": "Hyponychium - skin in front of toe tip, eponychium - living skin on top of cuticle"},
    "12": {"question": "What is your actual nail called?", "answer": "Nail plate"}
}

